qone8.com 2013-11-17

# Qone8.com

### Our Policy

Welcome to qone8.com, which belongs to Taiwan Shui Mu Chih Ching Technology Limited. Taiwan Shui Mu Chih Ching Technology Limited operates the website located at http://www. qone8.com and has created the Site to provide certain internet services to our users. This Privacy Policy sets forth the Company’s policy with respect to information, including personally identifiable data, and other information that is collected from Site visitors and users of the Services. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

Our goal is to become your favorite Internet destination by providing the information, services, and product offerings that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, the qone8.com must collect information so we can understand what makes you different from its millions of other unique users. While you are not required to register for any services on the qone8.com, some Products and Services may not function properly or may not be accessible unless you do. 

### How Do We Use and Share Information?

qone8.com uses the identifiable business and business professional information that we collect to operate our website, to offer a variety of business information products and services for use in making risk management and marketing decisions, and to carry out transactions that you request or authorize. qone8.com will not sell, rent or share registered user business contact information to unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes without the registered user's consent. In conjunction with D&B, qone8.com maintains a separate professional contacts directory in which your company and individual business contact information may be listed. qone8.com licenses our business and professional contact information to authorized resellers and third party businesses for marketing purposes. Being listed in qone8.com’s company databases and professional contacts directories offers benefits to businesses and business professionals, including identification and recognition in the marketplace and the prospect of beneficial commercial opportunities and partnerships. 

### Security

The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect guest information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. 

### Updates

qone8.com will update this policy from time to time so please check back periodically. When such changes occur, you will see the word "Updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of each site on the qone8.com. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing them. 

### Contact qone8.com

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Site or Services.   
Taiwan Shui Mu Chih Ching Technology Limited  
Addres:4F., No.405-1, Sec. 1, Zhongshan Rd., Banqiao Dist., New Taipei City 220, Taiwan (R.O.C.)  
Phone: 0225221200
